- +234-9011240757
- titiarowosoge@gmail.com
- 44 Shosanya ave, Ikotun, LagosNigeria

Hard skills Adobe Premiere Editing Attention to detail Motion Design Multitasking Animation Collaboration Adobe Aftereffect Storytelling

Experience

Video Editor & Motion designer

Freelance - Fiverr.com (2015- till date)

- Worked on over 100 social media video contents for clients over the years producing and editing dynamic pieces of content for social distribution.
- · Managed projects from start to finish
- Used Adobe premier pro, Adobe aftereffect to create, edit and animate weekly for use in client productions.
- Used creative video editing techniques to produce innovative content for a variety of various clients social channels.

Graphics & videos (2011- 2015)

Video Editor & Video Animator

- Spearhead a team of three to create 3 videos per week
- Created social teasers, Input music, graphics and effects to existing videos.
- Partnered with social, marketing and design teams to brainstorm and storyboard video concepts.
- Optimized YouTube videos with catchy titles, proper tags and background music, etc.





Titilayo Elikwu

Professional Summary

Professional video editor and motion designer with 6+ years of experience and advanced video editing skills with knowledge of the latest video editing software, tools and techniques.

Ensure all video content created is on trend and on-brand, consistent in style and quality, and optimized for search and user experience for all content channels, including social media(TikTok, Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, and Youtube), especially short-form contents. I am a creative and collaborative team player, always creating visual contents optimized for different platforms on social media.

Education

- Bachelor Degree of Law Ekiti state University
- LL.B: Law Nigerian Law School

2007-2013

Links

- https://titilayoelikwu.github.io
- www.linkedin.com/in/layo-elikwu-temllo